We actually have a few friends, don't
we, from China who've come to work in
the UK and they seem to enjoy to some
extent the more relaxed pace, the the
shorter hours. So, when I've spoken to
them about moving back to China, they've
sort of gone like oh, no, like going
back to super long hours and like
>> understand that. I think it would be Oh,
yeah, just the level of intensity is
totally different. Yeah, I think that's
probably a big reason why lots of people
choose to stay here long-term. It's just
like more relaxed. Like, yeah, your
leisure time is respected. Like, that's
just nice, isn't it?
>> It's it's the 9:00 to 5:00 culture, you
which is still even now is still a
really big part of
British working life. You come in around
9:00, half eight, 9:00.
>> 10:00 to 4:00, I swear. Most people I
know work pretty much 10:00 to 4:00.
Like, they'll arrive late, they'll leave
early, no one cares.
>> The first hour is almost like you're
kind of setting yourself up for the day.
>> Yeah, make a coffee, have a chat.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, exactly, get settled in. Whereas
you should have started work an hour and
a half ago.
>> Yeah.
>> And then
And then, yeah, you're like, well, you
know, it's it's half past 4:00. It's
4:30 now. I'm getting a bit tired. I've
kind of done most of my stuff. I can
finish some of it tomorrow or maybe it's
all done now, so I don't have to be here
anymore. Or you I mean, obviously, you
could start a new project and you think,
well, we can just do that tomorrow. So,
then it's about 4:30 and you just sort
of think, ah, I'll just go home. And
then, yeah, nobody really bothers that
much. Like, it's not a a criminal
offense, you know.
>> [music]